(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(CHUCKLES)
(ALARM WAILING)
CASE: Damn it!
Rear armor?
Shot to hell.
(MACHINE GUNS FIRING)
You better drop back...
It's the last lap.
We can win this.
Why don't this son
of a bitch just die?
Oil.
Out.
Smoke.
Finished.
Give me the napalm!
Nothing works!
Drop the tombstone.
On my mark. Three,
two,
one.
I got you now,
motherfucker.
Mark!
Shit!
Fuck!
That's how you want
to do it? Okay.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
He's still coming.
Our tank is exposed.
He's got us, Frank.
You have to drop back.
It's a quarter mile to
the line. I can make it.
Sayonara, Frankie.
Punch out.
I'm sorry.
Forty years.
Longer than
my marriage.
Sounds like
you're gonna
miss this place.
MAN 1: I still can't
believe they closed
it down. Just like that.
The only thing
I'm gonna miss
is my paycheck.
Well, it was honest
work for honest men.
MAN 2: I got a family
to feed, and there's
no work out there.
I hear they
might be hiring
down at the docks.
Five men, maybe.
Hey, thanks, man.
Thanks, Jensen.
MAN ON PA: Collect your
final paycheck and leave.
The main gate will be
locked in 15 minutes.
(MEN CLAMORING)
Get ready to be
ripped off, boys.
Collect your paycheck
and leave the premises
in an orderly manner.
The main gate will be
locked in 15 minutes.
Cash or check?
Better make it cash.
$300.
I worked 120 hours
the last two weeks.
Cash fee. Next!
Cash fee?
You wanted cash,
there's a fee.
You want a check
instead?
Seeing as the company's
out of business,
not exactly.
You don't like it,
there's the complaint
box. Next!
(SIRENS WAILING)
They never get it.
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
(CLAMORING)
We're honest workers.
We're just like you guys!
What the hell are
you doing here?
You bastards!
(GROANS)
Shit! Shit!
Ross!
You okay, Ross?
Rubber bullets,
the assholes!
Come on!
Hi, honey.
Hi. Sorry
I'm so late.
Nice day at work?
Yeah. Just fine.
Give me that shirt.
They called the riot
police. It got ugly.
I don't deserve you.
You're a good man,
Jensen Ames.
And it doesn't matter
what anyone else
thinks but me.
So, $300. That's
all they gave us.
We'll make it last.
We always do.
I'll start
looking tomorrow.
I think you're
forgetting that
I married you
for your
non-financial assets.
Did you now?
Mmm-hmm.
(BABY CRYING)
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
(SHUSHING)
(SOFTLY) Daddy's home.
Is it you who was
making all that noise?
JENSEN: What does little
Piper want? Want a story?
You know you
won't understand it.
But it will be good
practice for me.
What the hell.
Let's go crazy.
Something smells good.
Honey?
Suzy?
(JENSEN BREATHING)
OFFICER 1:
Stay on the ground!
Stay on the ground.
OFFICER 2:
Drop the knife!
Do not resist!
Stay on the ground!
Stay where you are!
Don't move!
Move.
Get up against
the wall.
(JENSEN SCREAMING)
Scrub yourself.
Stop.
Prisoner will
step back.
Happy holidays.
(LIPS SMACKING)
(SQUEALING)
(INMATES FIGHTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
They slipped.
Good morning.
Morning.
Morning, Warden.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
There goes the
baddest ass in
the yard.
Sound like you're
in love, homie.
I am.
Damn. I had to
wake up for this?
All right, is it
my imagination,
or is this shit
getting worse?
Like, what is this
supposed to be?
Oatmeal.
I think.
Man, how do you
fuck up oatmeal?
Who's the new guy?
Jensen Ames.
The driver?
Never heard
of him.
Oh, yeah, I saw
him race years
ago. He's good.
Did some time
upstate.
Killed his career.
Holder of the fastest
laps at Willard,
Union and Butler.
I hope he's as fast off
the track as he is on.
Never a dull day.
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
Heads up.
It's Pachenko.
So you're the
wife killer.
Takes a big man
to kill a woman.
I suppose you
rape kiddies, too.
You hear that,
everyone?
Guy kills women.
Rapes kiddies.
What do you think
we ought to do
about that?
Get down on the ground!
Down on the ground! Now!
Nobody move!
I guess he didn't
like the oatmeal,
either.
Well, you've
got stones.
Putting the hurt on
a Brotherhood general.
But right now,
that's the least
of your problems.
The warden does bad things
to people that mix it up
with the drivers.
(KNOCKS)
Prisoner 77119, ma'am.
Thank you, Mr. Ulrich.
This prison is the
home to murderers,
rapists and
violent offenders
of every kind.
The United States
penal system sends me
the worst of the worst.
But the men
you've provoked...
Well, let's just
say, Mr. Ames,
that the life term
you joined us for
may be a lot shorter
than you think.
I understand.
Tradition.
Soften up the new guy.
An ass-slapping good
time had by all.
(GROANS)
Foul language
is an issue
for me.
While looking
over your record,
I couldn't
help noticing your
occupational history.
It seems you
have some talent
behind the wheel.
Out of curiosity,
when was the last
time you raced?
It's been a while.
I lost my license.
What if I could
help you?
Get my license back?
I had something
else in mind.
You're familiar
with the Death Race
and the driver
the fans call
Frankenstein?
A man so disfigured
by crashes
that he's forced
to wear a mask.
His return to the track
is highly anticipated,
and therein lies
my problem.
No one knows yet,
but poor Frank died
on an operating table
not long after
his last race.
Anyone can
wear the mask.
But not just anyone
can drive the car.
You have the skills
I require to keep
the legend alive.
I want you to become
Frankenstein.
No, thanks.
He's dead.
Why don't you just
tell the truth?
The audience wants
to see Frank again.
He moves them.
Inspires them.
And in this world,
that's not so easy
to come by.
What makes you
think for a second
I would risk my life
doing this for you?
Win five races,
you go free.
Those are the rules.
And Frank
has won four.
Win one more,
you walk.
Call it intuition,
but...
I don't think you
belong in here
with the rest
of these animals.
I might surprise you.
The race is Friday,
and I need your
decision.
Ten seconds
from now, I will
retract this offer,
and extend it
to Prisoner 68815,
James Francis Barlini,
who, clearly not
of your caliber,
will be quite
enthusiastic about it.
And you, unfortunately,
will need to spend your
incarceration in solitary.
Since now I know your
dirty little secret.
I'm sure you'll find
solitary preferable
to what Mr. Pachenko
and his friends have
in mind for you.
You're a skilled
driver. Your
chances are good.
I'm offering you your
freedom, Mr. Ames.
If it's not worth
risking your life
for, what is?
All right, turn her up
and tighten the lines!
She's hemorrhaging!
Ma'am.
You don't have to
call me "ma'am."
You know that.
This is Mr. Ames.
You know why
he's here.
Oh, I do now.
The race is less
than a week away.
I have great
confidence in you.
Well, then,
I'll leave you two
to get acquainted.
Jensen Garner Ames.
Moved to the States
at 24 years old.
Named after a car,
the Jensen Interceptor.
A three-time local
speedway champion.
You've done your
homework. Or do you
just know everything?
Jensen Interceptor.
I had one.
Handled like
a school bus.
Call me Coach.
Everyone does.
Gunner. Lists.
This is Frank.
I'll show you around.
LISTS: We have a fully
functioning auto shop,
just like you'd find
in the outside world.
Each team has
their own shop.
We don't help them.
They don't help us.
To the inmates,
you're Jensen Ames,
the new grease monkey.
LISTS: Nobody will know
you're Frank except us
on the team
and a handful
of the guards.
Nobody will talk.
How can you
be so sure?
Hennessey.
In here, she is judge,
jury and executioner.
The race is her baby.
Anyone who threatens
it, she kills.
The audience for
the race has halved
since Frank's been
out of the game,
and so has the
corporation's profit.
That's why she needs you.
What's back there?
That's a good
question.
Hennessey's had a whole
wing of the prison in
isolation for a month.
Working on
something.
Time to meet
the Monster.
Mustang V8 Fastback.
Took the best
and made it better.
That's a V8 Roush
5.4 liter with a Ford
Racing supercharger
putting out
850 horsepower
and close to...
Seven hundred
pounds of torque
with sequential
multi-port fuel
injection.
Looks like there's
a 250 hp NOS unit.
Just in case.
Then we had some fun
customizing your personal
protection package.
Three-quarter
inch steel plate,
front and sides.
Bulletproof glass
will be here, here
and there.
And in the rear,
a six-inch solid
steel shield we call
"the tombstone."
Oil, smoke, and
napalm for defense.
And twin 30-millimeter
belt-fed machine
guns for offense.
So where's the ammo?
We get that
on race day.
Pity.
Yeah. Everyone
thinks that,
first time.
Thinks what?
About turning the
guns on the guards,
about escaping.
No, I wasn't
thinking that.
Well, I'm glad,
because
Hennessey has got
electric kill switches
in all the guns
in all the cars.
And all the guard
towers are fortified,
and their guns are
bigger than your guns.
But did I mention
the helicopters,
and also the fact
that we're on an
island here
a mile from the
nearest shoreline?
The only way in
or out of here
is on that one skinny
bridge you came in on.
What's that?
Most important
part of the car.
How many people
has Frank killed?
Twenty. The mortality
rate is average
62.2% per race.
So Frank beat the
odds four times.
Yeah. Till they
beat him.
COACH: The race takes
place in three stages
over three days.
The first two stages,
you just got to try
and get rid of
as much of the
competition
as you can
while getting
your own skinny ass
over the line alive.
Third stage is
where speed counts.
First one over
that line wins.
Tomorrow morning,
you meet your
navigator, Case.
She'll help you
navigate the course,
reload your weapons
and help with the
running of the car.
I'd like to talk to
her ahead of time,
before the race.
Yeah. I'd like
a big-tittie girl
to lick peanut
butter off my toes.
That ain't gonna happen.
It's still a prison,
man. She's a chick.
They get bussed in
from the women's
facility upstate.
It's all about ratings,
fast cars, pretty women.
Yeah, Machine Gun Joe
is the only one that
has a male navigators.
'Cause he's gay.
Actually, it's 'cause
he goes through
them so fast,
the audience
gets squeamish.
Yeah, he goes
through them.
Through their ass.
He cuts each kill into
his skin as a souvenir,
right here.
What about
the rest of
the drivers?
Lists?
LISTS: 14K.
First generation
Chinese-American,
10th generation Triad.
And his father sent
him to business school.
He's the only man
in here who holds
a degree from MIT.
He's killed four
men off the track.
GUNNER: That we know of.
Another seven
on it.
LISTS: Hector Grimm,
The Grimm Reaper.
The man's a master.
Clinical psychopath.
Believes that Hennessey
is an avatar
of the Hindu goddess
of death, Kali,
and that he is
her messenger.
Cuckoo.
LISTS: Three time
consecutive life
sentences.
He's killed six
men off the track,
another 12 on it.
You've already met
the local chapter
of the Brotherhood.
Their driver, Pachenko,
has killed nine men
on the track.
Nobody knows
how many off.
Travis Colt,
our local superstar.
Used to race
for NASCAR.
Yeah, he was
good, too.
Until he fell asleep
behind the wheel
of his Mercedes
with the help of
a bottle of scotch
and a handful of ludes.
Wiped out the entire
patio of La Scala.
Sent a dozen people
to the hospital.
God damn it!
It killed three of them.
Technically the best
driver in here,
but a mean son
of a bitch within.
MACHINE GUN JOE: Ladies.
I hear your man Frank
is still in the infirmary
with 15 unhealed fractures.
I also hear he's not
gonna make the race.
You hear a lot.
Who's the new fish?
Grease monkey.
Well, well. Monkey.
I got a new
name for you.
Igor.
'Cause you about the
ugliest motherfucker
in this prison, yo.
(MACHINE GUN JOE CHUCKLING)
Funny, huh?
You tell Frank
when you see him.
This race
is between
me and him.
This time won't
be no infirmary.
It'll be the morgue.
I'll be sure
to pass it on.
Let's get out
of here, man.
Man, that is
one angry homo.
Who are they?
Work detail.
Get to work on
the track for
good behavior.
Those are GPS
tracking bracelets.
In case somebody
decides to go
for a swim.
(PANTING)
HENNESSEY: The ring.
This was the
old Frank's.
It kind of melted
to his hand.
ALL: (CHANTING)
Frankenstein!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
Assholes.
He's all yours.
Don't talk to
the other drivers.
Frank never did.
Part of the mystique.
Let the mask
do the work.
Here comes trouble.
(ALL WHOOPING)
(MEN WHISTLING)
There's our girl.
I'm Case.
Frank.
Funny, you don't
sound like Frank.
Don't sweat it.
I know.
I drove with Frank.
I'll watch your back.
Better than you
watched his, I hope.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Still here. Well,
I guess I got to
work a little harder.
Get back to your
car, prisoner.
You sure know how
to make friends.
Case. This is
mirrored glass.
No one can see in,
so you might want
to take the mask off.
Unless you like
it under there.
How the hell did he
drive in that thing?
What?
You're better looking
than the last Frank.
A few crashes
should change that.
Start the transmission.
MAN: Three, two, one.
And we're live
worldwide.
ANNOUNCER:
Welcome to Death Race.
Terminal Island Penitentiary
hosts three days
of the ultimate
in auto carnage.
Stage 1 of the race
begins streaming
live in 10 minutes.
Subscribe to
Stage 1 now for $99,
or subscribe to
all three stages for
the low price of $250.
Access to over 100
live camera feeds.
Watch from the car of
your favorite driver.
See the action your way,
uncensored and unedited.
A full-on fight to the death,
featuring four-time
winner Frankenstein.
Three-time winner
Machine Gun Joe.
Pachenko.
Travis Colt.
Audience favorite
Frankenstein
resumes his bitter
grudge match
with Machine Gun Joe.
Frankenstein
returns to the track
after a six-month absence.
HENNESSEY:
They've missed him.
He's the man that
just won't die.
Twelve million hits
on his angle alone.
He hasn't even
started the engine.
We'll do 45 million
viewers today.
So, what are
you in for?
They say
I killed a cop.
Did you do it?
Yeah.
Bad cop?
Good cop.
Lousy husband.
Frank, Case,
you read me?
JENSEN: We hear you.
COACH: This is
a three-lap race.
Hennessey doesn't
activate the weapons
till lap two.
Now remember,
it's first come,
first served,
so it pays to
be out in front.
This is it. Countdown.
(ENGINES REVVING)
You're sure
he can deliver?
Jog left to 100 feet.
50, 20...
Now!
Punch it! Hard
left up ahead.
He seems to be
handling himself.
Wakey-wakey!
We're being passed.
We've gotta catch up!
Man, I know
what I'm doing!
Hey, just leave
that motherfucker...
Shut up, man!
I know what the
hell I'm doing.
What you gonna do?
You can't
go head-to-head
with Joe like this.
He'll tear you apart.
You read me?
Listen to him, before
you get us both killed.
Case, help him
out of there!
There's a shortcut
to the left.
There!
He's taking
the shortcut!
You don't think
I see that?
Activate swords
and shields.
The swords arm
the main guns.
Shields trigger
the napalm,
oil and smoke.
I know. I've seen
this race before.
You think you know.
It takes the weight
of the entire car.
You have to make contact
with all four tires
simultaneously.
Anything else
I'm missing?
Don't get me started.
Activate death heads.
Death heads activated.
Feel it, baby!
(LAUGHS)
(GROANING)
Score another one
for the Reaper, baby.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Come on. All clear.
Fuck you, puto!
Fuck you!
We got guns.
Look out. Oil.
(WHOOPS)
Damn!
Your mother's a puta,
motherfucker!
What the fuck?
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
We got to get
back in the race.
(SPEAKS CANTONESE)
(GRIMM GROANING)
I'm the fucking
Reaper, baby.
Can't kill me.
You can burn me.
You can fucking shoot
me, but you just can't
motherfucking kill me!
Get that off my window
when we get back.
We're streaming to
46 million viewers,
ma'am.
Offensive weapons are up.
It's on.
Fuck.
It's jammed.
Cover me.
Jesus Christ!
Hold tight, Case!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I'm back.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Shield up ahead!
That son of a bitch!
LISTS: He just stole
a shield from Colt!
Defense weapons are on.
Let him have it.
The napalm won't fire!
Smoke.
No smoke? No oil?
No napalm?
Again?
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
Fuck, man.
Remember me, motherfucker?
Coach!
The tombstone won't take
much more of this.
CCACH: Frank, Case, those
50 caliber shells will be
through the tombstone
in a matter of seconds.
My advice, either
lose him or kill him.
(LAUGHING)
Unhook the napalm.
Get on my lap.
What?
What the hell?
Merry Christmas, asshole!
Oh, shit!
(SCREAMING)
Nice work.
(CRASHES)
Where's he going?
A shortcut. Punch it.
We can beat him.
Look out!
(LAUGHING)
ANNCUNCER: Grimm,
Colt and Siad are gone.
Six remaining drivers alive.
Subscribe to Stage 2 now!
COACH: We have
14 hours, gentlemen,
so let's get to work.
Starting with this.
So what happened
out there, Case?
He got distracted.
He got distracted?
Coach!
What?
Look at this.
The oil sprayers
work fine.
Well, I'll
be damned.
Stop.
ULRICH: Last place.
It's too bad.
Look on the
bright side.
Everyone loves
a comeback.
What can I do for
you, Mr. Ames?
You sure are lucky
a driver like me
just happened
to turn up in your
prison when I did.
Oh, I'm more
than lucky.
I'm blessed.
Sometimes it's
like the right
hand of God
is sitting on
my shoulder.
I'm not racing tomorrow.
Go fuck yourself.
Wait.
Take his shackles off.
Please excuse us,
Mr. Ulrich.
And take Mr. James
with you.
Do you recognize
these people?
Because your
daughter will.
They're her
new parents.
What's her name?
Piper.
That's the man
she'll grow up
calling Daddy.
Unless you do
something about it.
Where is she now?
Oh, I'm sure I have
her address around
here somewhere.
You're a smart man,
Mr. Ames.
Play my game,
we both go
home happy.
The man who killed my
wife is in this prison.
I wonder what he'll
say when I ask him
why he did it.
Why don't you look
in a mirror? Ask him.
Poor Piper. It must be
hard growing up with
that knowledge.
That your father
killed your mother.
You wanted a monster.
Well, you've got one.
COACH: She has your eyes.
Her mother's.
So why don't you wear
a number, Coach?
Because I'm
not a prisoner.
I qualified for parole
three years ago.
Got as far
as the gate.
They got a name for it,
something-or-other
syndrome.
The simple fact is,
the world's changed
since I've been in here.
Don't know it.
Don't much want
to. But this?
This I know.
What did they send
you away for?
Oh, plenty.
And nothing.
To what do we owe
the pleasure of
your company?
I killed my wife.
Bullshit.
You're a hard man,
but you ain't no
wife killer.
How do you know?
I've met my share.
But you, the way
you looked at her...
You couldn't do that
if you'd killed her
mother. So...
I say bullshit.
Coach.
What would you say if
I told you Hennessey
had my wife killed
and me framed for it
so she could bring me
in here to be her
Frankenstein?
What would you say
to that bullshit?
Her name was Suzy.
I was always headed
here. Always knew.
She didn't.
She was my chance
at something else.
And that bitch took
her away from me.
"...that thy days may
be long upon the land
"which the Lord thy...
Giveth thee.
"Thou shalt not...
"kill."
You should
take a break.
Get some sleep.
I'm okay, Lists.
Concentration
for the race.
Concentration,
that's what you need.
Gotta get your rest.
Maybe you're right.
I will take that
break after all.
GUNNER: Good call.
Guy can't grind
for shit.
(GRUNTING)
Move!
Looking for me?
Hold him.
You killed my wife.
Well, now, maybe I did.
I don't care if
the queen bitch
wants to save you
for the track.
Nobody disrespects the
Brotherhood and lives.
Put him down.
I'm going to
take your head.
(GRUNTS)
(LISTS GROANS)
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
What the fuck!
(YELLING)
(SHOUTS)
Hennessey made me
do it. Ulrich...
Ulrich too.
Let me go, man.
I'll do anything.
You're going
to die here.
Fuck you!
Now, now, boys.
Let's save that
for the track, huh?
Coach!
Take a look at this.
GUNNER: What the hell were
they building in here?
COACH: We'll find
out soon enough.
ULRICH: Prisoner!
It's time to get ready.
ANNOUNCER: Welcome to
the next installment
of Death Race.
Stage 2 begins.
Grimm, Colt and
Siad are gone.
Six remaining drivers alive.
14K.
Pachenko.
Riggins.
Carson.
Three-time winner
Machine Gun Joe.
And starting from
the back of the grid,
his archrival, Frankenstein.
This could be the last time
we see Frankenstein race.
Just one more victory
and he wins his freedom.
If Joe doesn't
kill him first.
Over 50 million viewers
have already subscribed.
Don't miss this epic battle.
Subscribe to Stage 2, now.
(ENGINES REVVING)
Pay attention!
Where is he?
What are you doing?
What's he doing?
He's dropping back.
He's not even
trying to race.
We're gonna have
a little talk.
We're gonna be
done by the time
we leave the tunnel.
Did you kill
the old Frank?
What?
Tunnel comes up fast.
Remember what happened
to the napalm canister?
Be a real shame for
that to happen to you.
Did you kill
the old Frank?
I sabotaged his
rear weapons.
Why?
Hennessey.
She said she'd sign
my release papers.
It's my life back.
I'd have killed
him, too.
I didn't kill him!
He wouldn't quit.
I just wanted to
make sure he didn't win.
Why would Hennessey
want that?
To keep Frank
here, racing.
And yesterday?
She wanted me
to set you back.
So I'm not supposed
to win, either.
Just make it exciting.
That's all
I wanted to know.
Hold tight.
Come on!
Just come
on through!
Damn!
He's going
after Pachenko.
Sword and shield
ahead. Take defense.
No.
There's someone
I need to kill.
You're out in front.
Who are you going
to shoot at?
You're a dead man!
(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
I told you to
take defense!
He's too heavily
armored!
Fuck!
Hit the smoke.
(SCREAMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
This is a race.
You don't go
backwards.
And you don't get
out of the car.
It was Hennessey.
Hennessey.
I know. She's next.
I got it. Frank's
out of his car.
What?
He stepped out
of his car.
Okay. I see him.
I need guns.
Yes. Sword coming
up in 50 yards.
What happened?
I don't know.
Somebody must
have grabbed it.
What do you mean,
somebody grabbed it?
Look, man.
I thought it was lit.
What do you mean,
you thought?
Man, get the fuck
out of my car.
What?
I said, get the fuck
out of my car!
Oh, hell, no!
Come on, man.
Listen, we got...
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait!
It ain't my turn!
It's not what I do.
Get in there.
Don't let me
down, boy.
Release the Dreadnought.
Coach?
Oh.
Well, I guess we know
what she was building now.
Activate weapons.
Jesus Christ!
Coach, any ideas?
You just have to
tough it out, I guess.
Hennessey will take it
off after she's pumped
up the ratings.
You sure
about that?
Where the hell is
that thing going?
(SPEAKS CANTONESE)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Fuck me.
JENSEN: Lists.
Receiving.
I want you to
patch me through
to another car.
On it.
JENSEN: Joe?
Who is this?
It's Frank.
What do you want?
How about we play
a little offense?
I hope you know
what you're doing.
(WHOOPS)
(ALL CHEERING)
Now that's entertainment!
Damn it!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: Frankenstein!
Frankenstein!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
Nice reflexes
there, lgor.
Race car reflexes.
You look lost, pal.
Not this time.
I got this feeling
that you and Frank
are close.
Real close.
That weird accent.
You even kind of
sound alike.
I was wondering,
what if you got
in a accident?
Would that throw
Frank off his game
a little bit?
I doubt it,
sick, fucked-up
guy that he is.
He might just
want to kill you.
That's cool.
So I guess I'll
see him later.
Right?
Let's roll.
Ma'am, with all respect,
what are we going to do?
We're going to kill
him, of course.
You want me to
kill Frankenstein?
Don't be stupid.
Frankenstein
can't die.
After all,
he's just a mask.
HENNESSEY: Tonight is the
final leg of the Death Race,
and perhaps a new
champion will arise.
A five times winner.
The first man ever
to gain his freedom.
The world gave you to me
because you were not fit
to be a part of it.
You were not fit
to be husbands,
you were not fit
to be fathers,
and were too
dangerous to live
with the rest of us.
What is this
shit, man?
But when you race tonight,
know that the eyes of
the world are upon you.
And know that
the very same world
which rejected you
now lives and
breathes with you.
And it draws inspiration
from your courage.
No one is ever gonna
win five races.
HENNESSEY: So race well...
Nobody is ever
getting out of here.
...and know that
I consider you
all my heroes.
I want to show
you something.
GRIMM: Can't kill me.
Can't kill me. I'm
the fucking Reaper.
You can burn me.
You can shoot me.
But you can't
motherfucking...
There.
Gunner, Lists.
Will Hennessey's
inspectors care
if we had a half
gallon reserve tank?
Another half gallon?
You got a fuel tank
that holds 35 gallons.
What the hell
you want another
half gallon for?
Coach?
Let's give the man
what he wants.
Hey, where are
you going?
Oh, this is
not good.
Real brave,
coming over here.
I'm going to win this
race, 'cause I want
out of this shithole.
I've already won
three races.
Two more,
and I'm smoking
Cohibas in Miami.
Frank might want
to think about that.
'Cause I'm gone.
Out of here.
Then maybe
it's his turn.
Maybe he's thinking
it's the other way
around.
From here on out,
you stay the fuck
out of my pit.
Hey.
Thinking you and Frank
should have a little talk.
ANNOUNCER: Welcome to
the final installment
of Death Race.
Seven men dead.
Siad,
Grimm,
Colt, Pachenko,
Carson,
Riggins
and 14K are all dead.
Just Frankenstein and
Machine Gun Joe survive.
Frank, racing for
his freedom.
Joe, doing anything
to stop him.
It's mano y mano,
and there will
be no mercy.
Tonight, only one
man will walk off
this track alive.
A record 70 million
are already watching.
Join them.
Subscribe to the
final stage now.
It's an honor to
navigate for you,
sir.
They call me...
Save it.
We won't have time
to get acquainted.
GUNNER: What the
hell are those?
LISTS: Model 7
Russian states
armory RPG's.
Armor-piercing, self-arming,
accurate to 1,000 yards.
That's what
I thought.
Prisoner, step back.
I thought maybe
you could use a
little inspiration.
Your release papers.
They're already
signed.
All you have to do
is walk off that
track alive.
Well, and win,
of course.
But if you do win,
I want you to think
about staying here.
As Frankenstein.
With me.
Yeah.
I can see the appeal.
What would you do
with your freedom?
Go back to
your daughter?
That's the idea.
The thing is,
are you really
the best future she
could possibly have?
Are you really
daddy material?
Or deep down, are
you something else?
If you decided that out
there on that track is
where you belong,
it would be the most
unselfish act of love
I've ever seen.
Just something
to think about.
What's this?
Small modification.
So Hennessey tells me
if you're going to win,
I'm supposed to stop you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Sounds like the odds
are stacked against us.
Then do what
you do best.
Drive.
Gentlemen,
this should
be interesting.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Lit sword up ahead.
Deactivate that.
Sir?
Just do it.
Switch it back on.
Weapons are up!
Damn it!
Shit.
Lit shield up ahead!
Damn it!
What happened?
Hennessey must have
deactivated it. Bitch!
Light me up.
It's party time.
Coach, we gotta
get the firepower.
Nothing lit
for a half lap.
We won't last that long!
Drop the tombstone.
What?
Do it!
On my mark. Three,
two,
one!
Mark.
Damn it!
(SCOFFS)
That shit don't
work twice, playboy!
Shit.
Lit shield in
quarter lap.
Do you hear that?
Lit shield in the
quarter lap.
He's coming up fast.
Let them get the
shield. Keep the
viewers interested.
Son of a bitch!
He got the shield!
Arm the explosive.
Just in case.
Yo, Frankenfreak.
This villager's
got a pitchfork,
and it's headed
straight up your ass.
What just happened?
(ALL CHEERING)
LISTS: Yeah! Yeah, Frank!
They're off the track.
They're escaping.
They're headed
for the bridge.
Their weapons.
Hit the kill switches.
Seventy million
viewers, ma'am.
They're all watching.
Shut the webcast down.
Shut it down!
Shut the fucking
computers down now!
Get out! Get out!
Get out! Now!
Yo, Frankenstein.
It's good we had
that little talk.
We gave that bitch
a good show, huh?
Give me that!
Okay, cocksucker,
fuck with me,
and we'll see who
shits on the sidewalk.
Somebody's mad
right now.
Nobody fucks
with my car.
Son of a bitch!
Get the choppers
in the air!
Come on.
Off the ground.
Go, go, go!
(SIRENS WAILING)
So what's your
real name?
I don't have the
time for small talk.
Just want to know
who I'm riding with.
Jensen Ames.
Like...
Like the car.
Well, Jensen Ames,
I hope you got a plan,
'cause it's not like
we're going to
get very far.
You're right.
We won't.
Now would be
a good time.
Very nice modification.
COACH: That extra half
gallon reserve tank
should see you through
to the finish.
Bon voyage, Frank.
Choppers have
a visual, ma'am.
Good luck, Joe.
Get me a pilot.
I need to talk to
a pilot right now.
Okay. You're on.
Stay with Frankenstein!
Don't lose him.
Sure you're
up for this?
I'm sure.
I owe it to Frank.
Besides, Hennessey
already gave me my
release papers.
They have to let me out.
They've stopped
him, ma'am.
GUARD: Keep your hands
where we can see them.
You are under arrest!
I repeat, keep your hands
where we can see them!
You are under arrest!
Hey, lgor.
Merry Christmas.
Come on. Let's
get out of here.
Nice.
The fact you have
duds like these
might make someone
question your...
My taste?
Yeah. So to speak.
I don't know about you,
but I'm headed to Miami.
Miami's good.
I'll meet you
down there.
Once I got my baby girl.
It's a shame I didn't
get to take care of
that bitch Hennessey.
Yeah. That is a shame.
Frankenstein has
been retrieved.
And, ma'am, ratings
are off the charts.
Gifts and congratulations
are already coming in.
You win again.
Mr. Ulrich,
I always win.
Damn.
I love this game.
MACHINE GUN JOE:
So we had to fix
this car?
How many times
we gonna keep
doing this, man?
This car is not
gonna start.
(GROANS)
Damn it!
You say you want me
to live the life of
an honest man, huh?
Yep. You better
get used to it.
Hey, lgor.
Think we got
a little company.
What took you so long?
Had trouble getting
my release papers
approved.
Wait here.
There's someone
I want you to meet.
Look at her.
She has beautiful eyes.
They're her mother's.
MACHINE GUN JOE:
Where'd you get
the rims?
I won it.
Card game.
JENSEN: Yeah, right.
No, really.
How many
horsepower's
in this engine?
Five hundred.
You sure
about that?
JENSEN: Someone
once asked me,
did I think I
was the best future
for my little girl?
Something I've thought
about for a long time.
This is what I decided.
No one in this
world is perfect.
Heaven knows I'm not.
But I love her more than
anyone else possibly could.
In the end, that's
all that matters.
She's my chance
at something else.
Something better.
And there's no way
I'm letting go of that.
HENNESSEY:
Okay, cocksucker,
fuck with me,
and we'll see who
shits on the sidewalk.